Corey Clarke

Full Stack Developer

Profile

I am a passionate and enthusiastic Full-stack developer that specializes using React and Node. My expertise lies in translating designs into fully functional websites/applications while utilizing my development skills to enhance and customize their features. From a young age I fell in love with the world of technology and embarked on my journey of knowledge and growth within this field.

Very strong communicator derived from my previous experience in retail which has also shown me how to work fast-paced and under pressure. Thrives in a team environment but has no issue working alone.

In my leisure time I enjoy studying languages and attending the gym as well as creating personal side projects.

Employment History

Freelance Full-stack Developer, City of London

November 2023 — Present

Created and managed websites/applications using modern technologies while providing excellent customer service and support.

Personally consulted clients with design suggestions and hosting recommendations.

Create and optimize UI/UX designs to increase overall aesthetic appearance and improve conversion rates.

Customer Service Assistant at Lidl, East London

March 2020 — Present

Provided quality customer service to customers with issues that needed resolving.

Stocked and tidied shelves in preparation for the general days routine.

Counted inventory stock.

Trained junior staff members.

Frontend Developer Intern at Adobe, London

November 2021 — October 2022

Designed and developed user interfaces for web applications using Next.js and React. Worked closely with back-end developers to integrate front-end components with Node.js APIs. Implemented responsive designs and optimized front-end performance.

Education

BSc hons computing, Arden University, Holborn, London

November 2020 — December 2023

Graduated with 2:1

Details

Chingford, East London United Kingdom 07713076333 sombas100@yahoo.com

Links

Portfolio LinkedIn GitHub

Skills

Git

Node.js

HTML & CSS

React

JavaScript

TypeScript

MongoDB

MySQL

Sass

Redux

SCRUM/Agile

TailWind CSS

Python/Django

PostgreSQL

Languages

English

Korean